{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "He _________ taking the key.",
      "a": "admitted",
      "b": "managed",
      "c": "hesitated",
      "d": "hoped",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Admit + V_ing\n\n- Manage, Hesitate, Hope + To Verb",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The government ___ to lay down a railroad there.",
      "a": "avoided",
      "b": "gave up",
      "c": "postpone",
      "d": "decided",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Decide + To Verb Infinitive \n- Avoid, Give up, Postpone: + V_ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The student ___ to sit for the examination because he was ill.",
      "a": "expected",
      "b": "failed",
      "c": "meant",
      "d": "put off",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Fail, Expect + To Verb Infinitive. We choose \"Fail\" base on the meaning of sistuation: He is ill so he can not take part in the exam\n\n-Mean + To Verb: Plan to do something (Don't fit to the meaning of sistuation)\n\n- Put off + V-ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Did he appreciate ___ his mistakes?",
      "a": "you to point out",
      "b": "for you to point out",
      "c": "your pointing out",
      "d": "your being pointed out",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "Two ways can be used with \"Appreciate\":\n\n+ Appreciate + somebody + V_ing\n\n+ Appreciate+ Possessive adjective + V_ing\n\n- The answer \" your being pointed out\" is passive voice: not suitable to context of this sentence",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you considered ___ for a scholarship?",
      "a": "to apply",
      "b": "to be applied",
      "c": "applying",
      "d": "being applied",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Consider + V_ing \n- The answer \"being applied\" is passive voice: not suitable to context of this sentence ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I want to swim, but they do not allow ___ in this lake.",
      "a": "swimming",
      "b": "to swim",
      "c": "swim",
      "d": "to swimming",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Allow + (Without Object) Verb_ing\n\n- Allow + Object + o Verb Infinitive",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "We avoided ___ over the unpaved road by taking the new highway.",
      "a": "to drive",
      "b": "to be driven",
      "c": "driving",
      "d": "being driven",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Avoid + V_ing\n\n- The answer \"being driven\" is passive voice: not suitable to context of this sentence",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "That boy earns his living by ___ papers.",
      "a": "selling",
      "b": "to sell",
      "c": "having sold",
      "d": "to have sold",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Preposition (by, on, up...) + V_ing/ Objective\n\n- The tense of the answer \"having sold\" is present perfect: not suitable to the context of this sentence which is simple present tense",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I asked the man if he would mind ___ off the radio.",
      "a": "turn",
      "b": "turning",
      "c": "to turn",
      "d": "having turn",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Mind + V_ing\n\n- The tense of the answer \"having turn\" is present perfect: not suitable to the tense of this sentence",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "When questioned, the students denied _________ the practical joke.",
      "a": "to play",
      "b": "to have played",
      "c": "playing",
      "d": "having played",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Deny + V_ing \n- The tense of this sentence is past perfect ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}